[{"answer": "Have a seat right here.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "You know, I was -- I had to use the bathroom before I came out here.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Why can't we live like this?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "When you were a young little guy in -- in Indianapolis, did anybody inspire you?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I mean it wasn't Bing Crosby.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Did you have a favorite comedian or a comic or somebody?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "And I just thought there's something very cool about this.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "This is Merv.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "This is Merv right there?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "1969?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, it's a silly story, but where better to tell a silly story than here with you.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Did you -- did you have an eye for the show business at that point?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "But that's -- and I -- I can remember doing so poorly my mom was very upset about it and she said we're going to try to get you into a trade school.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "So then I -- then I stopped worrying so much about other things and just knew that all I have to do is find a way that you can get paid for what I thought I can do.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Isn't that nice?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, as a kid, I think most kids are always funny.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "And when did the comedy phase hit you that you wanted to be a comedian, you wanted to get involved in comedy?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, in a matter of speaking, yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "So one night you just packed up and drove to Hollywood?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "No, I'm coming across the table if you roll another tape.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I don't want anymore tape.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "It really bothers you that much?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "You think so?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Fine, thank you.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Miss Letterman, can I ask you a question?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes, he talks about it frequently.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Has he ever told you that?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Yes, but he made me very nervous because he was, I think, the biggest star on television.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Did you have a good relationship with Johnny?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Jack Paar?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "I understand exactly what you're saying.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Do you understand what I'm saying?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "All the time.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "But did you have a chance to tell him what he meant to you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I was -- I was --", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "And how did you feel when I said good-bye, when I moved on?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Honestly, I was puzzled because I thought there's no reason for you to retire.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Same feelings?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "\"Cabin Boy\", yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "\"Cabin Boy\"?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Big hit -- that's it.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Would you like to buy a monkey?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "It was excellent.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Not bad, huh?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Any aspirations to become an actor?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I did an acting bit in \"Hot in Cleveland\" recently.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "And if you're not going to be really good at it, what's the point of wasting everybody's time?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I played Pierre, a gay hair stylist.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "It's just something to do, right?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "George Miller, and when he was a much younger fellow, he had a narrowing -- and he periodically would have to run a hose -- down his esophagus to open it up.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I'm just saying.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why are you telling me that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Wasn't he?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Quadruple bypass surgery, yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Now -- but to be more serious about this, you went through a quadruple, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "He -- he and his family were going to Jamaica.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I remember that night and I remember not wanting to go back, not feeling ready to go back, but knowing we had to go back.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "You remember that night?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "No doubt about it.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "I mean, wasn't he the light that led everybody through it?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Well, you have to, because life is no longer solely about you.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "But that's the way you feel, isn't it?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Does he know what you do for a living?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "ETTERMAN: Yeah.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Does he laugh?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Momma's boy for sure.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Is he a momma's boy or daddy's boy?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "Believe me, I'm embarrassed about it as well.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "How have you been able to do that year after year?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "Not for me.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Is it a chore to come up with those?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "She's fine.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "How Regina?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Have you had a favorite guest over the years besides me?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 843, "question": "Remember that night?", "qSentId": 842}, {"answer": "Not now, Dave, I'm in the middle of a show.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "What are you doing out there?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "No, it was cute.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "Isn't that terrible?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "You know, that was -- these are so much fun, the Vespa Scooters.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Is this why you gave me this car when I left?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "It's not the two wheeler.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "You can't ride a bicycle?", "qSentId": 880}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 888, "question": "Is Regis here tonight?", "qSentId": 887}, {"answer": "You were nice enough -- You took the Vespa back and you gave me a beautiful watch.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 899, "question": "You have heard that before, haven't you?", "qSentId": 898}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "Are you wearing it now?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "If you want to sing, you sing.", "docId": "120529pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "We're not going to sing?", "qSentId": 915}]